

MUHAMMAD MUSTAQEEM

Product Design | UI/UX Designer

in Linkedin: mustaqeem1

☐ Email: m-mustageem@outlook.com

■ Phone: +92 342 3510876

Portfolio: www.theuxfixer.com

Location: lahore, Pakistan

About me

Hey I'm a Product Design & UI/UX Designer with great of experience in understanding and designing digital products from concept ideas to production. I work with my clients to help them create web apps and mobile apps from the ground up or to help them solve business problems through visual and usability improvements.

Education

BS-Information Technology

Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan (2015 – 2019) CGPA-3.0/4.0

Skills

Adobe Creative Suite FIGMA sketch CorelDRAW Balsamiq Invision **Usability Testing** User Experience (UX) Prototyping **Product Design** Wireframing **UX** Research Website Design Mobile App Design Mobile App Design Saas App **Product Design** User Interface Design **Branding & Identity User Stories User-centered Design** Visual Design Teamwork Team Leadership CSS JavaScript HTML

Licenses & certifications

Google UX Design Professional

May 2022

Google

UI/UX Designer

July 2019

Treehouse

Front End Developer

July 2019

Treehouse

Work Experience

Total 4+ years

UX Consultant at Citrok

Feb 2022 · Presen

In my position in the company as a UX consultant, I work on different kinds of products like CMS, SAAS, App design, and website and responsive solutions recently I am working on three projects which name was People Data Labs, ADSS and Usearch.

UX Designer at Thinkdone solutions

May 2020 - Jan 2022

My position in the company was as a senior UI/UX designer, I done many projects like Elevatyx product, Kelger Management website has been designed and also developed. I have also done Ecommerce products whose names are DrGlow website, MFC(Myfastcoaching) App, and KFC(Keto fast coaching) App.

UI/UX Designer at Xaavia Studios

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

I joined the company as a UI/UX Designer. I designed and created a complete professional branding suite for one of their the client mentioned Blackstone including the logo, Website design, Marketing material, and App graphics as well. I also designed the entire product of the Text Neck App launched by Moltyfoam and also Burnsroad House restaurant.

Bitsclan IT Solutions Pvt Ltd

Feb 2019 - Sep 2019

UI/UX Designer

After 3 months I was promoted to UI/UX designer. I designed a Urtasker website, which was an e-commerce solution as well as the entire product. Including some marketplace websites.

Graphic Designer

I will join this company as a Junior Graphic designer, I done many projects like logo designing, banner animation, etc.